Hello friends, good evening from America,
you must be having a
Gram Panchayat somewhere, we sent General
Singh's letter directly on Telegram, in the
morning I told you before 9:15 that there was a
good trade
apprentice here, you must have seen it from there,
I had explained the logic in Vodafone Idea as well and here on
Telegram we don't do it round and round
like other people, write such words,
Crucial Junction Sir, that is, it is at a very crucial juncture,
Big Moon, oh what kind of a place am I brother,
tell me something, what do you say, straight talk, no nonsense, this is what
happens on Telegram and those who
are present on Telegram and are enjoying, those who are
not there, they can search for Manish of the party
and you can do it on Telegram
friends, welcome to your own channel
TK Money, my name is Tribhuvan Anshan
Certified Inequity
Redish and this is what I told them that the new
people who are in the village,
you can also do a part by spending Manish of the person on the Telegram channel
and if I go somewhere or the other,
I see something  So I also do my police inspector work with you, whatever it is
I do myself, I will tell you and
I know many things and you are
seeing the results, there is
no need for me to tell you and let's start the discussion here, first of all on the
important thing, the
turmoil in the market, can the market crush, can the
market sink,
see before or around the USA elections,
it is certain that Donald Trump sir, somewhere or the other,
sir, I am getting to know that he is going strong, will the
market lapse,
but the US markets have already crushed,
but Nifty was saved today, Scorpio
is rolling in the market, what did I tell you yesterday, the levels which I had
given you, you have to stay above the zone of 73011, otherwise if you do
not stay there, there can be problems and
what happened, after worshipping the 1107 33k chart, it is
exactly on the same path from 7766 2011, there was a
tremendous collection in the market, copy
page collection came that it has definitely been like Bigg Boss,
a neutral secure zone, see this Monday
is more important than criminal,
from Reliance on the ground  It will hit you only then you
can see there are eight and a half cycles I
play beach point George Sainik, maybe if
I tell you then I will not update you or
on Telegram you know trade friend
first I share like 5 kg later the
boasting and this type of thing I do
not do first I will tell you what I am going to do
and the results are in front of you
so when the label phase stays above then only
we will make it otherwise we have to wait and
watch so the first stock here is
Vodafone Idea but you know the
place for getting the results of Vodafone Idea is definitely around 100 crores
but compared to the last quarter which is the very
last now there are a lot of one off items arre
you know about the past their astrology is
going on Izhar use and all the other things are
here and the second win
what is there in Vodafone Idea is a long time topic
Vodafone Idea is quite volatile I have told
you earlier also that investment will come, it can
show a lot of growth and here somewhere or the other the
results of Vodafone Idea were
okay and Pooja  Average revenue per
user, I think he has
found something around under 19. And secondly, I
told you that volatiles talk, only those who can
take risks should work, so I
always keep this in mind in trading
and I gave it to you today, so
I think you must have enjoyed Vijay,
as I said, it
opened down by three percent, you will remember this,
I told you earlier, representing A is
opening, as soon as it goes green, I have to
remind you, stop loss of one percent and
target 4%, then it went up to 67 percent,
okay, we have had our fun,
let others have their fun because
you know about intraday positions, I
field a little idea, I do not do investment boxing, I do some other related
jobs, other people who take more risks
also do work, take a
dip in it, okay, everyone has their own method,
here the results of Reliance Industries are about to
come, at the time I am making the video, the
results from my village have not come, I have
not seen them, but Reliance
Industries is somewhere or the other.  It is showing its movement
here, you can try it and
show it a good moment, I had discussed it with you
two days ago on Telegram when the
market was crushing around 2014,
Reliance Industries, see, it is
coming around the big support, from here somewhere there are
1 chances of it going up, that is, and I am
also in a slight mood to bank here,
I took a minute to go around 2211 when 1975, I had just
told you that it can go up there,
see here at the lower level, the ad by which
I want it, from here
it has definitely gone up 2% from the price, but
one thing is the result friend, that is, if the
results are good then I think it can
become a rocket, Reliance 4G runs on send alarm,
if the results
go normal then there can be some problem, looking at the
details of our discussion
on the gram, you know that it is clear, but for
long-term, some questions also
come around that, whatever we
need, everything that
I told you, this Reliance  If you are doing retail
business then there is no problem in taking
more than a little money around BookMeShow. I had stopped you from taking the route. Stop
now and it will
give its results. And from here 2000 came,
see here, that is why I say that you have to
react around the price, you will
not just take it, things do not work in one way, there are
investors in the market because it is
very important to book profit as well. That is why the
port sent in Bharti Airtel, we saw the
situation after the earthquake at 15%,
why did it come down now, that is why I say that you should not
just take it, you have to
withdraw the property, you have to take the update down at the right price.
Reliance is such a company, friends, it is a long term
stock, so there is no need to think or understand, it is an
absolutely great company
and in my opinion, as seen in the price section,
good results may come
and if this area of ​​2000 2020 gets filled, then there is
hope that we may
see an increase on the market and if something like this is
seen in Sunday trading, then I will
definitely share it with you on Monday.  I will do it and you know
I do
n't tell stories in America later, I
first set up my plant so that
you understand the stop loss,
now you don't spend time like you people doing fifty-sixty calls like this, there wo
n't be data like that, you just have 50 calls, 40 will
be wrong, now the 24 that will be correct, I am praised a lot about them, you should
check them by half, that too the things that I share
because I personally go through a lot of
care, the hybrid scooters, I do
n't share them with you right now, I always
say that whatever seems small to me,
I share with you, whatever is a
little more of it, I take it myself and
like it, okay, many times I have
tested it with you, I do the work myself during holidays,
but whatever I share on Telegram,
see, by telling the fortune stop loss
proper, so you can see here
that A Jawai Saheb Pension is a very good
company in the long term, it is a good stock
portfolio stock, that Bigg Boss f5 is
always present, always in his sight,
400  The price has come around, there
is definitely value here, you will have to put a five-point technical
chart, if you get some reading, then in
my opinion it is a good company, if it will
give some support around 400 then it is the make or
break point level, if this boss comes then it
is good, otherwise there can be some problem,
free TV can come, if it comes then it will come to take,
for long term investors,
in the long term, there is no doubt in the report police and Dadar, it is a
high quality company, it is a
good brand, they can definitely pay attention here
and I always pay attention to all these things, side start ad, one
sewing, Baje Alive agency, CMC,
send me your information, if you
know about them from old followers then it is a good company, there is
no doubt, if I see something, I will
share it in cosmetic America also, if I
see it, it is
somewhere around a very important
zone in Chittor, after looking at the section, decide, you will get
support only and the stock should be
played, hey, let me leave it, when we see, what is
happening here on Monday, they are saying 1.5, so here it is very
important, 1.5 million
people lights, so it is certain when 40% volume is
running a little low.  Because the
interest of friends on you is more,
I am not seeing the maximum of potato, they
increase the volume here, then if some news comes, then
friends jump more to buy and
sell, that is why the volume is strong, so at
this time if you see, the
volume in potato hour is weak, so the
stock in the volume is exactly like that of
PM, which I had said that there is a trend from 2018 to 28,
which will keep moving in the range
until these triggers come and do
you know the trigger, the results are of better
type, only when they come, then this moment will
come and I still stand by what I told you earlier, the fault is going to come
around Diwali,
many people had gone that
its results will come before the line, what did I
say, it will come around Diwali and will
come close there because see here, what
they have said in it, it says anti-oxidant,
that the result has to be given in 35 days of France,
so Ravana happened,
this happened 2030 days ago, I remember one summary, if I did
not pay attention properly, then I think it happened in
that manner around Diwali  The
results of 18 should come and will
come around the same, let me tell you a week in advance, if Hazare
comes soon then it would be better
that Akshay had this personal experience before the company, there is no
doubt that there will be
bad results in the market, but here I want
my personal and if my personal opinion is
correct then the market does not seem to be supported,
Pujyashree is going to happen and there will be no support, it will
break the top songs, remember
support resistance is very important
in the stock market and
in technicals, worry things are displayed here, you know
that most of the indicators of technical lines
follow service talk money,
but this service talk has been
associated for some time now, it has become a normal top,
but this is the topic, despite that
we have seen this and that and cassettes,
you have seen the old people, so here or
there the ad movement is
visible, so look here, next Josh
Talk is such a good MP3 company, very high
quality, so if there was support around 2016,
now after this it went around like and Twenty-20,
police were here  The result is fine, there were
some profit declines
but this is a good company, it is not a long term
gainer, it is a stock with statement tips, it
also gives all the dead of 12,
as I know, and often
stay in the portfolio through join messages, no matter what, or Nikunj,
this is also a company stuck in MC business
somewhere, and the technical level,
The Bhootnath, I had told you, there were
some levels of 2008, but if you
give support here, then it seems that you will be around 100,
I do not have a big support,
because such times happen, these are
Prince's Business Chowk and some good
pharma companies do not remain, if you remember, then
here we are not covering it, so there is no
fear, if the company sinks, then we will give extra
tax, this is 6 inches, from here Bigg
Boss, there is no intention of returning 10%,
I have definitely come here like a share,
I was told that it is quite high,
so fundamentally, somewhere or the other, someone will come
How can we assume that the deal happens, it gets washed away and the
player becomes completely subdued, so this is
with Amazon, this is about Amazon losing
face with its partner,
something interesting I can't remember the
name, but if this deal happens then it is
fine, then the support will hold
and then you can see my support,
but if this does not happen then the support will break,
remember, first of all
I will tell you that before the good results come, the
results break because
everyone knows that Bigg Boss knows, so
this cannot happen, so in
my opinion something must be
there, something must be there, there should be a
wearable for Future Retail, especially for the
pair, in all the groups,
I only track Future Retail and I do
not track the rest for some time,
I know much about this, no, no, to
say, Tuesday was the wrong thing, the company was
experimenting and it increased, due to this there was
definitely a problem and in the last six months there was a lot of
problem, due to this all these
problems have happened, tell me at a level definitely technical,
if 7577 comes out then  A little bit of
hope can increase, remember this,
we should keep it in the middle of the resistance area under this
65th position, if the support is
not broken then it is good, I have not taken any previous and I have not taken any
pressure
in the stock, I do not want to say that I am tracking it, it gives
your interest, hence if there is a little
love disease, please turn on the notification of these videos
and your fans.